Tell me Sir, I keep saying again and again that Ani ji doesn't like anything, it's not like that, I don't like anything, I
say that I like whatever I like, I don't
like that, so let me tell you the
bad ones first, otherwise Deep will
say that you are giving all the bad ones today, full
of IC, it has given excellent results, it has a
very strong and good performance on every parameter,
this company of The General Insurance 186 7, this will be your stop loss
level,
buy for three targets of 1900, 1915 and 1930, good result,
strong results, better than expected,
this stock can show good action today on every parameter, this is the
opinion to buy on this result, just to make you happy,
I am coming back to my old
track, I am opinion to sell,
Reliance 1 40, your stop loss will be 3050,
3020 and
2990, according to the results, the decline from
705 to 00,
chemical business is weak, retail is weak,
gas exploration is not much fun
Telecom is doing well, that means for the first time
Reliance 1, there will be such weakness in a day or two.
Opinion to sell in Vipo futures.
Sell with a stop loss of 5566. 534, 523, 520 and
515 are all the levels for which selling has to be done. This is the
worst result in the entire IT sector.
I cannot say it is the worst. It is because of this that the
price has fallen, even though the numbers were
not bad. Look, the stock falling is one thing, the
result being bad is another thing. So it
fell because it was big earlier. People
expected such a bad crash, that is why the
fall is because of high expectations.
This is very bad, so I
think it is going to fall very hard.
They have already reduced the guidance by weakening it.
Outlook is not good. There is only one company
whose outlook is looking bad. Results are also
bad. Outlier ADR reduced at 11, 12. There
is a big fall here. I think it should fall at 5, 6.
After that, let us see if there is follow
up selling or not. Opinion of Vip to sell. Well,
these are some stocks.  At this time
Anil ji will give you more stocks at 9:00
and of course budget cheap shares, you also have to buy this
with sir, so this programming is yet to come.